Documentation - Kid Larry

OVERVIEW:

Thank you purchasing and/or downloading the Kid Larry Animations package!
Kid Larry is a character based off myself & designed for 2d sidescrollers, platformers, brawlers, etc.

The FREE version includes the following movement animations & will be updated with any other traversal animations I decide to add:

- Idle
- Walk
- Run
- Crouch / Pre-Jump / Land
- Jumping
- Falling
- Crouch Walk

The paid version includes the above animations as well as the following combat animations:

- Quick Attack 1
- Quick Attack 2
- Quick Attack 3
- Strong Attack 1
- Strong Attack 2
- Strong Attack 3
- Strong Attack 3 Alt
- Hit 1
- Hit 2
- Knocked Down

When used correctly, quick & strong attack animations should seamlessly flow into one and other creating amazing looking combo attacks.

HOW TO USE:

1) Locate the character you wish to apply the animations to.
2) Ensure it has a Animator & a Animator Controller attached to it.
3) Drag & drop the Kid Larry animations from the project folder to the Animator window. (Window > Animation > Animator)
4) Trigger the animations via a script of your own making.

DISCLAIMER:

The Kid Larry Asset is sold as a set of animations & not a character controller.
It is up to you design your own character controller to use with the provided animations.
I will, however, endeavour to provide a character controller in the future, Thanks!

CONTACT INFORMATION:

My name is Larry, I'm a muppet, and I make, play, & review games.

🐧 Twitter.com/LarryIRL 
📸 Instagram.com/LarryIRL_ 
😁 facebook.com/LarryIRL
🔴 Twitch.tv/LarryIRL
📺 Youtube.com/channel/UCBlwt8HeEG7Nfnhvq5SiBSA

Much ❤️ my friends!

🎮Games 🎨Art 🎵Music 📸Vlogs